Jiang Lai and Sheng Yuanzhou
So that's the kind of relationship they have
Looks like you don't like me in this dress
I'll change it
It really is her
Should've brought it with me
You actually found out
You sent me the message
What do you want
Mess with you
Just have a little fun
You said I'm trashy
You look down on me
And I'm pissed
So I had to get it back somewhere else
Tell me
In what way am I worse than Lin Siqi
My body, my looks
My abilities
Even my wealth
My family is much better off
Didn't think you were the jealous type, Jiang Lai
In our circle
A fling is pretty normal, isn't it
A fling
He doesn't know what we really are
I'm warning you
Don't play this kind of joke on me again
My patience has limits
Let me remind you
I'm not the only one watching you
My guess was right
This is getting more and more interesting
Mr. Sheng
This is the guy who
followed you and Ms. Lin Siqi that day
His name is Liu Dazhuang
He's unemployed
Liu Dazhuang
Liu Dazhuang used to be a pro boxer
After an injury, he retired and fell apart
He drank all day
Had a nasty temper
His wife couldn't take it and ran off
Leaving their young daughter with him
But due to his neglect
So she died of illness in her teens
Liu Dazhuang couldn't accept her death
He went to the hospital and caused a scene
And stabbed his daughter's attending physician
Got 9 years and 6 months for Intentional Assault
He was just released
Lin Siqi's mom was her attending physician
Yes
Did you find his address
He's been at his old place since he got out
The number you dialed is busy
I'm almost there
Zhang Xiaobei, get in
Lin Siqi's been taken
He did it on purpose
To shake us off
Then what do we do
Why are you on the phone right now
Shut up
I don't care how you do it
Within ten minutes
find me a
vehicle with the license plate Hai BF0304,
a Jinbei van
Hello
We've got the exact location
I've sent it to your phone
I've notified the police
Mr. Sheng, you don't need to go yourself
What if...
I'll handle it myself
Uncle Liu
Liu Xia wasn't killed by my mom
She died from illness
My mom and I were devastated too
Shut up
It was obviously a misdiagnosis
Xiaxia was perfectly healthy
Our place was cold in winter
Even without a stove
she never felt cold
And she never got sick
She did get cold, and she did get sick
You just didn't notice
Bullshit
Don't try to blame me
All of you said
that I killed my daughter
That I caused her to get sick
I loved her
I loved her more than anything
I'll prove it to you today
How much I loved her
If you rush in like that
What if you set him off
So we just wait here for the cops
What if he suddenly attacks
Calm down. Here's what we do
You rush in
And grab his attention
I'll go get her out
If things get dangerous
you run first
Staying alive comes first
You hear me
Stay calm
Go
Xiaxia
Daddy's gonna avenge you today
Snap out of it, Uncle Liu
Liu Xia wouldn't want to see you like this
Weren't you two good friends
Perfect, you can go keep her company
And atone for your mom while you're at it
Who's there
It's me
I'm the security guard
Xiaobei
I heard some noise over here
What's going on
Security
Yeah
No one's managed this place in ages
Why is there security
Our company just bought this land
We have to patrol every day
To prevent anyone from stealing these materials
Don't be scared
I heard some residents reported recently
that there's a suspicious person around here
How about this
Come with me to the security office
Let's get your info registered, all right
Let's go
Get out of here, now
Hurry, get out of here
The car's outside! Hurry
Xiaobei
Hurry
Liu Dazhuang has been brought to justice
We'll take care of it
Pick a time tomorrow
Come to the station to give a statement
Thank you
Thanks for what you did just now
I'm just glad you're okay
Did your family have a grudge against Liu Dazhuang
But it was all a misunderstanding
I met Liu Xia when we were little
At Jiang Lai's house
Jiang Lai's house
Uncle Liu was the gatekeeper there at the time
And Liu Xia would stay in the guardhouse
My mom was Jiang Lai's attending physician
So she took me with her on house calls
The three of us were about the same age
And we were all girls
So we started playing together right away
Your mom was Jiang Lai's attending physician
So the one Liu Dazhuang stabbed was...
It was my mom
Uncle Liu firmly believed back then
that my mom misdiagnosed her
and that's what got Liu Xia killed
So he rushed to the hospital
and stabbed her
But my mom still signed a Letter of forgiveness
Because she said
he was just a grieving,
pitiful father
You and your mom
are both really gentle people
Why does Sheng Yuanzhou care about me so much
The two of them have changed so much lately
Xiaobei
Why don't you care about what happens to me
But why was Liu Dazhuang so sure
that your mom misdiagnosed her
That's the strange part
Jiang Lai had leukemia back then
They'd already issued a Critical condition notice
Then one day she suddenly got better
But while she was recovering
Liu Xia suddenly came down with leukemia
and died
While one person's illness improved
another got the same disease and died
They were the same age
and the same gender
Could it be...
that Liu Xia used the Key of Fate too
and exchanged fates